Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Miscellaneous agreements (Box 175)
  - Pratt-Whitney Chandler Evans, 1964-1966 (Box 175, Folder 146)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1965 (Box 175, Folder 147)
  - American Airlines, Inc. -and- T.W.A. AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 175, Folder 148)
  - Agreements GMC AFL-CIO, 1940-1948 (Box 175, Folder 149)
  - Eastern Airlines -and- Airline Pilots Association International, 1960 (Box 175, Folder 150)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. -and- Air Line Pilots Association International, 1964 (Box 175, Folder 151)
  - Agreement between Eastern and the Airline Pilots Association International, 1965 (Box 175, Folder 152)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- I.A.M., 1963 (Box 175, Folder 153)
  - Employees Rules and Regulations Eastern (Box 175, Folder 154)
  - Pan American World Airways -and- The Airline Pilots Association International, 1962 (Box 175, Folder 155)
  - Pan American World Airways, Inc. -and- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers Express and Station Employees AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 175, Folder 156)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. -and- I.A.M., 1955 (Box 175, Folder 157)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. -and- T.W.U.A., CIO, 1959 (Box 175, Folder 158)
  - T.W.A. -and- The Airline Pilots Association International, 1965 (Box 175, Folder 159)
  - T.W.A., Inc. -and- The Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association, International, 1960 (Box 175, Folder 160)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc, -and- I.A.M., 1958 (Box 175, Folder 161)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. -and- The Airlines Pilots Association, International, 1959 (Box 175, Folder 162)
  - TWA -and- I.A.M., 1962 (Box 175, Folder 163)
  - TWA -and- I.A.M., 1962 (Box 175, Folder 164)
  - TWA -and- The Airlines Stewards and Stewardesses Association, Local 550 AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 175, Folder 165)
  - TWA -and- I.A.M., 1964 (Box 175, Folder 166)
  - TWA -and- I.A.M., 1964 (Box 175, Folder 167)
  - T.W.A. and I.A.M. (Box 175, Folder 168)
  - TWA -and- I.A.M., 1961-1963 (Box 175, Folder 169)
  - United Airlines, Inc. -and- The Airline Pilots Association International, 1957 (Box 175, Folder 170)
  - Airlines, 1960-1966 (Box 175, Folder 171)
  - The Firestone Tire and Rubber Company -and- U.R.C.L.P.W.A., CIO, 1955 (Box 175, Folder 172)
  - Labor Agreement and Pension Plan Agreement, 1963-1967 (Box 175, Folder 173)
- Miscellaneous - Ford Motor Co. Decisions (Box 176)
  - Memorandum Decisions M-523 thru M--1093 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum Decisions M-1094 thru M-1891 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Ronald W. Haughton RH-453 thru RH-1153, 1951-1953 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Ronald W. Haughton RH-1 thru RH-452, 1950-1951 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - David P. Miller Decisions 1 thru 503, 1952-1955 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - HHP 1-, 1952-1956 (Box 176, Folder 6)
- Borden Chemical PVC Division, Leominster MA and International Chemical Workers Union Local 553 [folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 177, Folder 1)
- Borden Chemical PVC Division, Leominster MA and International Chemical Workers Union Local 553 [folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 177, Folder 2)
- Sylvania Electrical Products and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1948 (Box 177, Folder 3)
- Boston Edison and Utility Workers Union of America Local 369, 1953 (Box 177, Folder 4)